(Leonard:)Sheldon, we've been through this.
I'm taking Penny.
(Sheldon:)Afraid not. Do you recognize this?
-Oh, not the roommate agreement.
-Indeed, the roommate agreement.
(Sheldon:)I call your attention
to the Friendship Rider...
...in Appendix C: Future Commitments.
Number 37:
"In the event one friend is ever invited
to visit the Large Hadron Collider...
...now under construction, he shall invite
the other friend to accompany him."
(Leonard:)Oh, for God's sakes.
(Penny:)You actually put that
in an agreement?
We put in what happens
if one of us wins a MacArthur Grant...
(Leonard:)...or if one of us gets superpowers,
or if one of us is bitten by a zombie.
(Sheldon:)He can't kill me. Even if I turn.
Is there anything about
if one of you gets a girlfriend?
(Sheldon:)No, that seemed a little far-fetched.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, do you really expect
to enforce this?
I've lived up to my commitments
under the agreement.
(Sheldon:)At least once a day I ask how you are,
even though I simply don't care.